messengeroo.com 2018-05-10

# Privacy

**MessengeRoo Privacy Statement**

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all MessengeRoo websites (a.k.a. blogs) including all the websites run under the www.messengeroo.com domain.

Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our [contact form](http://www.messengeroo.com/contact/).

**Email, Addresses, Name, Telephone Third Party Ads**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**  
Ownership of Information**

MessengeRoo is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

**Comments/Message Boards**

Most MessengeRoo websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Cookies**

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**

Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. MessengeRoo does not have access to this data.

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but MessengeRoo may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**

If MessengeRoo is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.  
**  
Links**

MessengeRoo websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by MessengeRoo

**Notification of Changes  
**  
When MessengeRoo makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.messengeroo.com/contact/).
